var quizQuestions = [
    {
        question: "1-What is Lizâ€™s favorite night-time food?",
        choices: ["Night chips", "Night fries","Night cheese","Night pizza"],
        correctAnswer: "Night fries"
    },

    {
        question: "2-What is the name of Jack's ex wife?",
        choices: ["Bianca ", "Sally","Liza","Molly"],
        correctAnswer: "Bianca "
    },

    {
        question: "3-When a clip is shown of Tracy Jordan (Tracy Morgan) running through traffic in his underwear, what is he shouting?",
        choices: ["I am a Jedi!", "I am Superman!","I am LL!!","I am a lion"],
        correctAnswer: "I am a Jedi!"
    },
    {
        question: "4-Before Tracy Jordan came onboard the show, who was the star of TGS?",
        choices: ["Jenna Maroney", "Mindy Lahiri","Leslie Knope","Lucille Bluth"],
        correctAnswer: "Jenna Maroney"
    },
    {
        question: "5-Liz Lemon works as the head writer for /TGS with Tracy Jordan/. What does TGS stand for?",
        choices: ["The Girlie Show", " The Gangster Show"," The Gremlin Show","The Grown-Up Show"],
        correctAnswer: "The Girlie Show"
    },
    {
        question: "6-Kenneth the Page, played by Jack McBrayer, is from which state?",
        choices: ["Georgia", "Florida","Alabama","New York"],
        correctAnswer: "Georgia"
    },
    {
        question: "7-On what night does /TGS with Tracy Jordan/ air in the /30 Rock/ universe?",
        choices: ["Friday", "Monday","Sunday","Tuesday"],
        correctAnswer: "Friday"
    },
    {
        question: "8-Who is the producer of /TGS/?",
        choices: ["Pete Hornberger", "Tracy Jorgan","John Donaghey","Liz Lemon"],
        correctAnswer: "Pete Hornberger"
    },
    {
        question: "9-Which writer does Frank, played by Judah Friedlander, share an office with?",
        choices: ["Toofer" , "Josh","John","Kenneth"],
        correctAnswer: "Toofer"
    },
    {
        question: "10-Liz goes on a rampage when she overhears who call her /the C word/",
        choices: ["Lutz", "Dot Com","Cerie","Grizz"],
        correctAnswer: "Lutz"
    }

];

var winImages = [
    "/assets/images/win1.gif",
    "/assets/images/win2.gif",
    "/assets/images/win3.gif",
    "/assets/images/win4.gif",
    "/assets/images/win5.gif",
    "/assets/images/win6.gif",
    "/assets/images/win7.gif",
    "/assets/images/win8.gif",
    "/assets/images/win9.gif",




];

var lossImages = [
    "/assets/images/loss1.gif",
    "/assets/images/loss2.gif",
    "/assets/images/loss3.gif",
    "/assets/images/loss4.gif",
    "/assets/images/loss5.gif",
    "/assets/images/loss6.gif",
    "/assets/images/loss7.gif",
    "/assets/images/loss8.gif",
    "/assets/images/loss9.gif",

];